Guide to the Constance Stuart Larrabee collection, 1935-2000 COR0011.MS
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Constance Stuart Larrabee collection
1935-2000
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Larrabee, Constance Stuart
COR0011.MS
9 Linear Feet 6 record center boxes
Constance Stuart Larrabee (August 7 1914-July 27 2000) was a photographer and South Africa's first woman war correspondent in World War II. Throughout the 1950s-1990s, Larrabee's photographs were displayed and travelled in various individual and group exhibitions, including several exhibitions at the Corcoran Gallery of Art. The Constance Stuart Larrabee collection includes artifacts, correspondence, exhibition files, photographs, negatives, and publication files of Constance Stuart Larrabee, photographer and South Africa's first woman war correspondent. A bulk of the materials document Larrabee's time in Europe as a correspondent and photographer during World War II. Materials date from 1935-2000.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Corcoran Institution Board of Trustees donated these records to The George Washington University in 2016.
Arrangement
Arranged in 4 series: Photos, contact sheets, and negatives; Publications and textual materials; WWII Documents and artifacts; and Exhibitions.
Biography
Constance Stuart Larrabee (August 7 1914-July 27 2000) was a photographer and South Africa's first woman war correspondent in World War II. Her work has been exhibited internationally and nationally across the United States, including in several exhibitions at the Corcoran Gallery of Art.
Born in Cornwall England, Stuart moved with her family to South Africa when only a few months old. As a teenager and young adult Larrabee studied photography in London, England and Munich, Germany before returning to South Africa and opening the Constance Stuart Portrait Studio in Pretoria in 1936. She opened a second studio in Johannesburg in 1946. While working as a portrait photographer, Stuart also began photographing South Africa's Bushmen, Zulu, Ndebele, Lovedu, Swazi, Sotho, and Transkei peoples.
In 1944, Stuart was appointed by the director of South African Military Intelligence as South Africa's first woman war correspondent. Stuart covered the Allied invasion for Europe for the South African magazine Libertas, travelling throughout Egypt, France, and Italy. Following her time photographing the war and immediate aftermath, Stuart returned to South Africa in March 1945 and had several solo exhibitions. Stuart published writings and photographs of her experiences during the war in a memoir named "Jeep Trek" in Spotlight magazine in 1946.
Constance Stuart married American Colonel Sterling Larrabee in 1949, moved to a waterfront farm near Chestertown, Maryland in 1950, and became an American citizen in 1953. At this time, Larrabee began breeding champion Norwich and Norfolk terriers. In 1983-1984, Larrabee founded Washington College Friends of the Arts in Chestertown, Maryland.
Throughout the 1950s-1990s, Larrabee's photographs were displayed and travelled in various individual and group exhibitions. Noted exhibitions include Edward Steichen's The Family of Man in 1995, solo exhibition Tribal Photographs at the Corcoran Gallery of Art in 1984, Frances Fralin's The Indelible Image in 1985, and solo exhibition WWII Photo Journal at The National Women of Women in the Arts in 1989.
In 1997 Larrabee donated her African photographs to the Smithsonian Institution's National Museum of African Art, her World War II photographs to the Corcoran Gallery, and her photographs of the Eastern Shore to the Chesapeake Bay Maritime Museum. All three institutions exhibited this work simultaneously in 1998.
Constance Stuart Larrabee died at her home in Chestertown, Maryland on July 27, 2000.
Constance Stuart Larrabee personal and professional chronology
1914 August 7 Born in Cornwall England. Three months later sailed with her family to Cape Town, South Africa. Lived on a tin mine in the northern Transvaal.
1920-1933 Moved to Pretoria. Given her first camera, a Kodak No. 0 Box Brownie. In 1930 won First Place in Photography, "Boys and Girls Achievement Week," Pretoria Agricultural Society.
1933-1935 Attended the Regent Street Polytechnic School of Photography, London. Apprentice in two professional portrait studios in Soho and Berkeley Square.
1935-1936 Advanced studies at the Bavarian State Institute for Photography, Munich. Introduced to the Rolleiflex camera, which she used throughout her career.
1936-1949 Established the Constance Stuart Portrait Studio in Pretoria. In 1946 opened a second studio in Johannesburg.
1937-1949 Began her lifelong interest in photographing South Africa's vanishing ethnic cultures: the Bushmen, Zulu, Ndebele, Lovedu, Swazi, Sotho and Transkei peoples.
1944 Solo exhibition: The Malay Quarter. Opened by Noel Coward in Pretoria. Traveled to Cape Town.
1944-1945 Appointed by the director of South African Military Intelligence as South Africa's first woman war correspondent on behalf of Libertas magazine. Served in Egypt, Italy, France, and England. Attached to the American Seventh Army in France, and accredited to SHAEF, Supreme Headquarters Allied Expeditionary Force. In Italy she was attached to the South African Sixth Armoured Division, under the command of the American Fifth Army, and the British Eighth Army.
1945-1946 Solo exhibition: A Tribute to the South African Sixth Division and the United States Seventh Army. Traveled through South Africa. Published "Jeep Trek" in Spotlight magazine.
1947 Solo exhibition: The Lovedu, Pretoria. Official photographer for the Royal Visit to the three British Protectorates of Basutoland, Swaziland and Bechuanaland. Kalahari Desert expedition to photograph the Bushmen.
1948 Produced portfolio of photographs on the author Alan Paton and his book, Cry the Beloved Country. Photographs published in: Bantu Prophets in South Africa by Bengt Sundkler (London: Camelot Press, 1948).
1949 Married Sterling Loop Larrabee of Warrentown, Virginia, U.S. Military Attache to South Africa, Yugoslavia (government in exile) and Greece during World War II.
1950 Moved to a historic, waterfront farm near Chestertown, Maryland. Began breeding champion Norwich and Norfolk terriers.
1952 Photographs published in: The Basuto by Hugh Aston (London: Oxford University Press, 1952).
1953 Solo exhibition: Tribal Women of South Africa, The American Museum of Natural History, New York. Traveled in the United States and Canada through 1957. Became an American citizen.
1955 Group exhibition: The Family of Man, Museum of Modern Art, New York. Traveled nationally and internationally.
1959 Solo exhibition: The Silent Harmony of Hand and Mind, the story of Steuben crystal, the Commercial Museum, Philadelphia. Traveled nationally.
1979 Solo exhibition: Photographs by Constance Stuart Larrabee, a retrospective, the South African National Gallery, Cape Town. First solo show by a woman photographer at the National Gallery. Traveled to the Johannesburg Art Gallery and the Pretoria Art Museum as the first photographic exhibition in each museum.
1982 Solo exhibition: Celebration on the Chesapeake, Washington College, Chestertown, Maryland. In honor of the college's bicentennial. Traveled within Maryland and to Philadelphia.
1983 Catalogue: Celebration on the Chesapeake, published by King's prevention Press and supported in part by a grant from the Kent County Arts Council. Solo exhibitions: The Constance Stuart Larrabee Celebration, 1933-1983, The South African Association of Arts, Pretoria, and The Art Gallery, University of Stellenbosch, South Africa. Nagmaal 1947, The Photo Gallery, The Market Theatre Foundation, Johannesburg.
1983-1984 Founded Washington College Friends of the Arts, Chestertown, Maryland.
1984 Solo exhibition: Tribal Photographs, The Corcoran Gallery of Art, Washington, D.C. Traveled to the Santa Fe Center for Photography, Santa Fe, New Mexico.
1985 Group exhibition: The Indelible Image: Photographs of War, 1864 to the Present, The Corcoran Gallery of Art, Washington, D.C. Traveled to The Grey Art Gallery, New York University, New York, and The Rice Museum, Houston, Texas. Catalogue. Solo exhibition: Go Well My Child, in collaboration with Alon Paton, The National Museum of African Art, Smithsonian Institution, Washington, D.C. Photographs now in the permanent collection of the National Museum of African Art. Catalogue.
1986 Group exhibition: Bon Voyage, The Cooper-Hewitt Museum, Smithsonian Institution, New York. Honorary degree of Doctor of Arts from Washington College, Chestertown, Maryland.
1987 Solo exhibition: Seek What Is True, in collaboration with Alan Paton, Duke University Museum of Art, Durham, North Carolina.
1988 Solo exhibitions: African Profile, Bayly Art Museum, University of Virginia, Charlottesville, Virginia. Seek What Is True, Mead Art Museum, Amherst College, Amherst, Massachusetts.
1989 Chairman, Washington College Friends of the Arts, Chestertown, Maryland. Endowed the Constance Stuart Larrabee Creative Arts Center, Washington College, Chestertown, Maryland.
1997 Donated her African images to the Smithsonian Institution's National Museum of African Art, her World War II pictures to the Corcoran Gallery, and her views of the Eastern Shore to the Chesapeake Bay Maritime Museum.
1998 Smithsonian Institution's National Museum of African Art, the Corcoran Gallery, and the Chesapeake Bay Maritime Museum simultaneously exhibited the newly-donated collections.
2000 July 27 Died in her home in Chestertown, Maryland.
Scope and Contents
The Constance Stuart Larrabee collection includes artifacts, correspondence, exhibition files, photographs, negatives, and publication files of Constance Stuart Larrabee, photographer and South Africa's first woman war correspondent. A bulk of the materials document Larrabee's time in Europe as a correspondent and photographer during World War II. Materials date from 1935-2000.
Bibliography
Biographical information sourced from the exhibition catalog for Constance Stuart Larrabee: World War II Photo Journal, The National Museum of Women in the Arts, Washington, D.C., 1989.
Art; Artists; Photography; War correspondents; Washington (D.C.); World War, 1939-1945; Corcoran Gallery of Art
- Photos, contact sheets, and negatives, 1935-2000; Series 1
  Arrangement
  Arranged in 5 subseries: Pre-WWII contact sheets and negatives; WWII contact sheets and negatives; WWII prints; Portaits; and Exhibition and installation openings.
  Scope and Contents
  Contains contact sheets, negatives, and press prints taken by Constance Stuart Larrabee in Egypt, England, France, Germany, and Italy while studying photography and while working as a war correspondent for South Africa during World War II. Also includes photographs of Constance Stuart Larrabee throughout her life taken by unidentified photographers and installation shots of exhibitions of Larrabee's work. Materials date from 1935-2000.
  - Pre-WWII contact sheets and negatives, 1935-1936; Series 1 subseries 1
    Contains contact sheets and negatives taken by Constance Stuart Larrabee in Germany and England while studying photography. Materials date from 1935-1936.
    - Munich, Germany [306405-500 1], 1935-1936; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Munich, Germany [306405-500 2], 1935-1936; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Munich, Germany [306405-500 3], 1935-1936; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Munich, Germany [306405-500 4], 1935-1936; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Munich, Germany [306405-500 5], 1935-1936; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Munich, Germany [306405-500 6], 1935-1936; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Munich, Germany [306405-500 7], 1935-1936; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Munich, Germany [306405-500 8], 1935-1936; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Munich, Germany [306405-500 9], 1935-1936; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Munich, Germany [306405-500 10], 1935-1936; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Munich, Germany [306405-500 11], 1935-1936; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Munich, Germany [306405-500 12], 1935-1936; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Munich, Germany [306405-500 13], 1935-1936; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Munich, Germany [306405-500 14], 1935-1936; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Munich, Germany [306405-500 15], 1935-1936; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Munich, Germany [306405-500 16], 1935-1936; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Munich, Germany [306405-500 17], 1935-1936; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Munich, Germany [306405-500 18], 1935-1936; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Munich, Germany [306405-500 19], 1935-1936; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Germany/England [306405-500 20], 1935-1936; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Germany/England [306405-500 21], 1935-1936; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Germany/England [306405-500 22], 1935-1936; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - England [306405-500 23], 1935-1936; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - England [306405-500 24], 1935-1936; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Munich, Germany [306405-500 25], 1935-1936; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Munich, Germany [306405-500 26], 1935-1936; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Munich Hitler Propaganda [306405-500], 1935-1936; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - WWII contact sheets and negatives, 1944-1945; Series 1 subseries 2
    Contains contact sheets and negatives taken by Constance Stuart Larrabee while working as a war correspondent throughout Egypt, France, Germany, and Italy. Materials date from 1944-1945.
    - Text and negatives w/o contact sheets, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 1, Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Copy negatives, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 1, Box 2, Folder 2)
    - CSL On All Fronts - London, 1944-1945; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 1, Box 2, Folder 3)
    - CSL On All Fronts - Egypt, 1944-1945; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 1, Box 2, Folder 4)
    - CSL On All Fronts - Germany and Italy, 1944-1945; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 1, Box 2, Folder 5)
    - CSL On All Fronts - Paris, France, 1944-1945; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 1, Box 2, Folder 6)
    - CSL On All Fronts - France, 1944-1945; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 1, Box 2, Folder 7)
    - CSL On All Fronts - Italy, 1944-1945; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 1, Box 2, Folder 8)
    - CSL On All Fronts - Paris, France, 1944-1945; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 1, Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Italy - SA Div. Castiglione cemetery and graves, 1944-1945; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 1, Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Italy - 6th SA Div. Castiglione scenes, 1944-1945; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 1, Box 2, Folders 11-15)
    - Italy - 6th SA Div. R.N. Carbiniers, 1944-1945; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 1, Box 3, Folders 1-2)
    - Italy - 6th SAD Grizzana wits De la Rey, 1944-1945; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 1, Box 3, Folders 3-7)
    - Italy - 6th SAD Lagaro, 1944-1945; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 1, Box 3, Folders 8-11)
    - Italy - 6th SAD Grizzana HQ, 1944-1945; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 1, Box 3, Folders 12-14)
    - Italy - 6th S.A. Div, 1944-1945; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 1, Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Italy - 6th SAD Grizzana, 1944-1945; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 1, Box 3, Folders 16-17)
    - Italy - 6th SAD Grizzana life, 1944-1945; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 1, Box 3, Folders 18-19)
    - Italy - 6th SAD General and Mrs. Theron Cairo, 1944-1945; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 1, Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Italy - 6th SAD, 1944-1945; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 1, Box 3, Folders 21-22)
    - Cairo, Egypt, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 1, Box 3, Folders 23-34)
    - Egypt Cairo Alexandria - minesweepers, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 1, Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Cairo Egypt Alexandria minesweepers, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Egypt, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Egypt En Route to Cairo, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Box 1, Folders 3-5)
    - South France, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Box 1, Folder 6)
    - South France - dead Germans, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Box 1, Folder 7)
    - South France - Liberation, Gaumont, D-Day Dolly, Marseilles, Red Cross, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Box 1, Folder 8)
    - South France, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Box 1, Folder 9)
    - French villager, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Box 1, Folder 10)
    - South France - invasion, St. Maxime-beach head, pilots on road, Marquis in car, 1944 August; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Box 1, Folder 11)
    - South France - invasion on beach, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Box 1, Folder 12)
    - South France - St. Maxime beach head, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Box 1, Folders 13-14)
    - South France - SA Pilots, sisteron and on road to Marseilles, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Box 1, Folder 15)
    - South France - German prisoners, field hospitals, liberation day on route to Paris, bombed kitchen stove, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Box 1, Folder 16)
    - South France - S.A. pilots, airstrip, 1944 August 8; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Box 1, Folder 17)
    - London, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Box 1, Folders 18-19)
    - Paris, France, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Box 1, Folders 20-23)
    - South France - Eve Curie, boots by parachute, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Box 1, Folder 24)
    - South France - Liberation Day at front, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Box 1, Folders 25-27)
    - South France, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Box 1, Folders 28-30)
    - South France - Gen DeGaulle, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Box 1, Folder 31)
    - South France - Gen DeGaulle, gen de Lide Tassigny, Troops reviewed, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - South France, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - South France - Invasion pilot over front line, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - South France - Invasion, no man's land, Jack Aldridge, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - South France - Invasion, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - South France - Strasbourg, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Folders 6-8)
    - Italy - Florence, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Folders 9-12)
    - Italy - Naples, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Italy - Pisa, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Folders 14-15)
    - Italy - Cassino, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Italy - Naples, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Folders 17-18)
    - Italy - Rome, St. Peter's, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Folders 19-21)
    - Italy - Rome, statues, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Italy - Rome, soldiers, 1944; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - 6th SA Div 3 and 7 wing bombers, Adriatic, 1944-1945; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Folders 24-25)
    - Italy - San Marino, 1944-1945; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Italy - San Marino, views, white oxen, 1944-1945; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Italy - San Marino, village life, 1944-1945; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - S.A. 6 Division - sixth birthday celebration, 1945 February 1; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Egypt - Cairo, 1944-1945; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - France, 1944-1945; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - WWII prints, 1944-1945; Series 1 subseries 3
    Contains press prints taken by Constance Stuart Larrabee while working as a war correspondent and portraits and candids of war correspondents, including of Constance Stuart Larrabee. Materials date from 1944-1945.
    - Press prints: Woman opening window, circa 1944; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 2, Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Press prints: Boy with gas mask, circa 1944; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 2, Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Press prints: Soldiers on tank, 1944; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 2, Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Press prints: D-Day Dolly, circa 1944; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 2, Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Press prints: Man standing on statue of a foot, Rome, 1944 August; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 2, Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Press prints: Collaborator, St. Tropez France, 1944 August 27; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 2, Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Press prints: Pour La Liberation, circa 1944; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 2, Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Press prints: General Charles de Gaulle, circa 1944; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 2, Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Press prints: Dead German soldier, circa 1944; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 2, Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Press prints: Detainees, Castiglione, Italy, 1945 January 5; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 2, Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Press prints: Vino + Venus, circa 1944-1945; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 2, Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Press prints: Old woman with kettle, circa 1944-1945; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 2, Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Press prints: Two soldiers standing, circa 1944-1945; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 2, Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Press prints: Boy playing instrument, circa 1944-1945; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 2, Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Press prints: Boy with large gun, circa 1944-1945; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 2, Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Press prints: War correspondents, circa 1944; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 3, Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Press prints: Two collaborators, circa 1944; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 3, Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Press prints: Little girl, seated, circa 1944; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 3, Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Press prints: Man holding onto boots, circa 1944; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 3, Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Press prints: Fallen German soldiers, 1944; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 3, Box 1, Folder 5)
    - War correspondents: Constance Stuart Larrabee skiing, circa 1944; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 3, Box 1, Folder 6)
    - War correspondents: Constance Stuart Larrabee with 5 men by car, circa 1944; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 3, Box 1, Folder 7)
    - War correspondents: Eve Curie, circa 1944; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 3, Box 1, Folder 8)
    - War correspondents: Man going through barbed wire (Jack Aldridge), circa 1944; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 3, Box 1, Folder 9)
    - War correspondents: Constance Stuart Larrabee with four soldiers, circa 1944; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 3, Box 1, Folder 10)
    - War correspondents: portraits of Constance Stuart Larrabee, circa 1944-1945; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 3, Box 1, Folder 11)
    - War correspondents: slightly out of focus close ups of a woman laying down, circa 1944; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 3, Box 1, Folder 12)
    - War correspondents: Woman on plane, holding glasses, circa 1944; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 3, Box 1, Folder 13)
    - War correspondents: Two men speaking on plane, circa 1944; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 3, Box 1, Folder 14)
    - War correspondents: Woman typing inside plane, circa 1944; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 3, Box 1, Folder 15)
    - War correspondents: Men crouching down with camera on tripod, circa 1944; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 3, Box 1, Folder 16)
    - War correspondents: Close up of woman with hat, circa 1944; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 3, Box 1, Folder 17)
    - War correspondents: Three women and one man inside a plane, circa 1944; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 3, Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Press prints: Couple at an outdoor restaurant, circa 1944; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 3, Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Press prints: An American and a French soldier, circa 1944; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 3, Box 1, Folder 20)